Ravshanov Avazbek

■ avazbekravshanov2@gmail.com □ 821080708714 🛅 https://www.linkedin.com/in/avazbek-ravshanov-ben96
■ https://avaz-tech.github.io/my-portfolio/

SUMMARY

As a great communicator, outcome-focused and process-oriented professional with overall almost 2.5 years experience, I am seeking a challenging opportunity to become Software Engineer where my advanced skills, education, extensive training and years of experience fully utilised

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Light Vision Inc

December 2022 - Present, Seoul, South Korea

- Extended AI Parking app capabilities through a new feature page developed using Flutter. Seamlessly integrated this functionality into the existing system, enhancing the user experience and customer escalation by 15% providing a user-friendly interface for efficient parking management.
- · Developed Admin page from scratch using React, Bootstrap, @mui Material, Highcharts to manage online video conferencing platform
- · Built video re-identification website swiftly with an intuitive, user-centric design using HTML, CSS, Javascript and Bootstrap.
- Demonstrated proficiency in developing and designing open-source video conference application, leveraging cutting-edge technologies and best practices to deliver exceptional user experience for visually impaired people.

Web Developer

Contract

April 2022 - December 2022, Seoul, South Korea

• Developed an intuitive online library website using React, Firebase for the Institute of Retraining of Pedagogic Personnel, improving user experience and mission alignment by reducing load time by 66% compared to the original.

Teacher Assistant

Samarkand Economics and Service Vocational College | IT Department

October 2015 - May 2016, Samarkand, Uzbekistan

- · Collaborated with professors to deliver instructions in C and C++ programming, providing hands-on assistance and guidance to students
- · Conducted code reviews, provided feedback, and helped students improve their coding skills.

SKILLS

Base languages: C, C, C, PHP

Web development: Javascript, Typescript, Next.js, NodeJS, React, Redux, HTML, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, @Mui material, Tailwind, Webpack

Mobile development: Flutter, Dart, Kotlin

Development environment: VSCode, Android Studio, Xcode

Others: JIRA software, Confluence, Postman, Git

Soft skills: Teamwork, Quality control, Problem-Solving skills, Communication skills, Train staff, Team performance monitoring

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science and Engineering

Sejong University · Seoul, South Korea · 2022 · GPA 3.5

Awarded 20%~60% scholarships for 5 semesters due to grades

College Diploma, Computer Technologies

Samarkand Economics and Service Vocational College • Samarkand, Uzbekistan • 2016 • GPA 4

CERTIFICATIONS

TOPIK - Level 4

National Institute for International Education, Seoul, South Korea • 2023 Proficiency in Korean language.

IELTS - Level 7

British Council, Tashkent, Uzbekistan · 2017

Proficiency in English language.